[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "When you look at this extraordinary life that you've led, when do you think your primetime was?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "this", "extraordinary", "life", "that", "you", "'ve", "led", ",", "when", "do", "you", "think", "your", "primetime", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "I think it started at about 62 when I became single for the third time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "started", "at", "about", "62", "when", "I", "became", "single", "for", "the", "third", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "mean", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, to really bring all of yourself, including the not always very attractive and perhaps not loveable parts of yourself to the table in a relationship, to -- it makes you very, very vulnerable.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "to", "really", "bring", "all", "of", "yourself", ",", "including", "the", "not", "always", "very", "attractive", "and", "perhaps", "not", "loveable", "parts", "of", "yourself", "to", "the", "table", "in", "a", "relationship", ",", "to", "--", "it", "makes", "you", "very", ",", "very", "vulnerable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Or was it both?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "was", "it", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, it was definitely me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "definitely", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "What have you -- what have you learned about yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "--", "what", "have", "you", "learned", "about", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "That I'm resilient, that I'm brave, that I'm honest.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "I", "'m", "resilient", ",", "that", "I", "'m", "brave", ",", "that", "I", "'m", "honest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "What do you make of what's going on with politics in America at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "with", "politics", "in", "America", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "I am -- I'm scared, I'm scared.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "--", "I", "'m", "scared", ",", "I", "'m", "scared", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "When you look at it, what do you think went wrong?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "it", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "went", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I can't answer the question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "answer", "the", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Are you blaming me there, Jane?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "blaming", "me", "there", ",", "Jane", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "I don't know you well enough.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "you", "well", "enough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jane"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "I mean, how far do you think the media -- the media has been complicit?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "far", "do", "you", "think", "the", "media", "--", "the", "media", "has", "been", "complicit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I think it's been quite complicit.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "been", "quite", "complicit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Who impresses you and who scares you?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "impresses", "you", "and", "who", "scares", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "They all scare me, frankly.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "all", "scare", "me", ",", "frankly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ":", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Even -- I mean even someone like a Newt Gingrich or a Mitt Romney, do they scare you?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "--", "I", "mean", "even", "someone", "like", "a", "Newt", "Gingrich", "or", "a", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "do", "they", "scare", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I'm worried about anybody getting elected to office who says we have to do away with or privatize Social Security, we have to reduce medical -- health insurance, we have to not raise taxes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "worried", "about", "anybody", "getting", "elected", "to", "office", "who", "says", "we", "have", "to", "do", "away", "with", "or", "privatize", "Social", "Security", ",", "we", "have", "to", "reduce", "medical", "--", "health", "insurance", ",", "we", "have", "to", "not", "raise", "taxes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "What do you think of Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I hope he gets re-elected.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "he", "gets", "re-elected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "What do your suspicions tell you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "your", "suspicions", "tell", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "What do you think, Jane, when you look at yourself in \"Barbarella\"?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", ",", "Jane", ",", "when", "you", "look", "at", "yourself", "in", "``", "Barbarella", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "I think it's a charming camp movie, not very sexy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "charming", "camp", "movie", ",", "not", "very", "sexy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jane"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "I mean, why did you feel -- not uncomfortable, but why are you -- why wouldn't you be that keen to be a sex symbol?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "why", "did", "you", "feel", "--", "not", "uncomfortable", ",", "but", "why", "are", "you", "--", "why", "would", "n't", "you", "be", "that", "keen", "to", "be", "a", "sex", "symbol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I'm 74 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "74", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ava Gardner"]}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "-- of all the -- who was the sexiest of all the stars you've ever seen?", "question_tokens": ["--", "of", "all", "the", "--", "who", "was", "the", "sexiest", "of", "all", "the", "stars", "you", "'ve", "ever", "seen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Ava Gardner as a woman.", "answer_tokens": ["Ava", "Gardner", "as", "a", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "If you were to tell me what really has excited your passions in life, on a chart list of top three, where would acting fall?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "to", "tell", "me", "what", "really", "has", "excited", "your", "passions", "in", "life", ",", "on", "a", "chart", "list", "of", "top", "three", ",", "where", "would", "acting", "fall", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CD", ",", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "There have been moments in some films when it feels transcendent, when it is the most wonderful feeling when you have entered someone else's reality and you know you're there.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "have", "been", "moments", "in", "some", "films", "when", "it", "feels", "transcendent", ",", "when", "it", "is", "the", "most", "wonderful", "feeling", "when", "you", "have", "entered", "someone", "else", "'s", "reality", "and", "you", "know", "you", "'re", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBZ", "``", "VBG", "NNP", "''", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ":", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Which is the movie that if you could be remembered for one you would choose?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "is", "the", "movie", "that", "if", "you", "could", "be", "remembered", "for", "one", "you", "would", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "ONDA: Well, I think the one I'll be remembered for is \"Coming Home\" because it was such a beautiful movie and such a universal -- so many girls have fathers that had a hard time loving them and people really identified with that movie and I think it really -- you know, a lot of people said to me, men and women, but mostly women, I saw the movie and then I went and I brought my father to see it and it changed our relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["ONDA", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "one", "I", "'ll", "be", "remembered", "for", "is", "``", "Coming", "Home", "''", "because", "it", "was", "such", "a", "beautiful", "movie", "and", "such", "a", "universal", "--", "so", "many", "girls", "have", "fathers", "that", "had", "a", "hard", "time", "loving", "them", "and", "people", "really", "identified", "with", "that", "movie", "and", "I", "think", "it", "really", "--", "you", "know", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "said", "to", "me", ",", "men", "and", "women", ",", "but", "mostly", "women", ",", "I", "saw", "the", "movie", "and", "then", "I", "went", "and", "I", "brought", "my", "father", "to", "see", "it", "and", "it", "changed", "our", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "``", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Which is yours?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "is", "yours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "I have a favorite, which is -- well, it's \"On Golden Pond.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "favorite", ",", "which", "is", "--", "well", ",", "it", "'s", "``", "On", "Golden", "Pond", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "What kind of relationship is that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "relationship", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "Well, you know, like a -- like a father and a daughter.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "like", "a", "--", "like", "a", "father", "and", "a", "daughter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "When you look back on that, Jane, what was the experience like for you working so closely with your father?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "on", "that", ",", "Jane", ",", "what", "was", "the", "experience", "like", "for", "you", "working", "so", "closely", "with", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "I feel so blessed, Piers, to have been able to have that experience.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "so", "blessed", ",", "Piers", ",", "to", "have", "been", "able", "to", "have", "that", "experience", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jane"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "What would you think the honest portrayal of your father would be as a father?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "think", "the", "honest", "portrayal", "of", "your", "father", "would", "be", "as", "a", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Well, let's start with the man.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "start", "with", "the", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "If you were analyzing yourself, what -- how would you describe your character?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "analyzing", "yourself", ",", "what", "--", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "your", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "WP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "I don't see myself particularly as feisty.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "see", "myself", "particularly", "as", "feisty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "But what do you think your father would have made of the way that you have turned out?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "do", "you", "think", "your", "father", "would", "have", "made", "of", "the", "way", "that", "you", "have", "turned", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Well, he pretty much knew the way I had turned out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "pretty", "much", "knew", "the", "way", "I", "had", "turned", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "How are you going to get me back into shape with this DVD then?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "get", "me", "back", "into", "shape", "with", "this", "DVD", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well, first of all, you've got to do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Have you learned to -- to love yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "learned", "to", "--", "to", "love", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I grew up thinking that if you weren't perfect that no one would love you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "grew", "up", "thinking", "that", "if", "you", "were", "n't", "perfect", "that", "no", "one", "would", "love", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "How many times do you think you've properly been in love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ve", "properly", "been", "in", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Oh, maybe five times.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "maybe", "five", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Well, if I -- but if I forced you to take one of the men you've loved in your life, who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "I", "--", "but", "if", "I", "forced", "you", "to", "take", "one", "of", "the", "men", "you", "'ve", "loved", "in", "your", "life", ",", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "You -- you couldn't.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "--", "you", "could", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "What do you think the biggest misconception about Marilyn was?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "biggest", "misconception", "about", "Marilyn", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "ONDA: I was very, very drawn to her.", "answer_tokens": ["ONDA", ":", "I", "was", "very", ",", "very", "drawn", "to", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marilyn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Is -- was that always going to be the way that someone as genius like but tormented as him was going to go?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "--", "was", "that", "always", "going", "to", "be", "the", "way", "that", "someone", "as", "genius", "like", "but", "tormented", "as", "him", "was", "going", "to", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", ":", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Just because one is absolutely brilliant doesn't mean you have to be screwed up.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "because", "one", "is", "absolutely", "brilliant", "does", "n't", "mean", "you", "have", "to", "be", "screwed", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "When you look back at it all, with the exception of marriage and the birth of children, what would you say has been the greatest moment of your life?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "at", "it", "all", ",", "with", "the", "exception", "of", "marriage", "and", "the", "birth", "of", "children", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "has", "been", "the", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Are you looking forward to humiliating Anderson on New Years Eve?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "looking", "forward", "to", "humiliating", "Anderson", "on", "New", "Years", "Eve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "I really live for that night.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "live", "for", "that", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111230pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "You could get him off air?", "question_tokens": ["You", "could", "get", "him", "off", "air", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "I know I can.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "I", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]